<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My blog</title><link>http://example.org/de/</link><description>Recent content on My blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Everything is mine</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 14:29:50 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>http://example.org/de/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 14:29:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/de/about/</guid><description>about DE</description></item><item><title>Convento da Vila Colheita DOC (2017)</title><link>http://example.org/de/wines/convento-da-vila-colheita-doc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 14:29:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/de/wines/convento-da-vila-colheita-doc/</guid><description>Syrah, Alicante Bouschet and Touriga Nacional: an eclectic blend of amazing grapes. 15 months from harvest to your glass. You will get a dark ruby red wine with intense mature red fruit fragrances, or should I say grapes that endured some of the highest temperatures of the country? Best enjoyed with red meat, fatty fisch and soft cheese. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to invite your friends!
Link</description></item><item><title>Portugal</title><link>http://example.org/de/region/portugal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 14:29:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/de/region/portugal/</guid><description>Vinho Verde Verde stands for green. Yes green, there is a green wine out there and it grows in Minho, a region on the very north of Portugal that rhymes exquisitely with &amp;ldquo;vinho&amp;rdquo; and funilly enough it is one of the greenest in the whole country. No surprise then that this is home to the DOC region of vinho verde grapes that you will find nowhere else in the world. Back in the days, thanks to a glitch in the fermentation process, the wine ended up having more &amp;ldquo;bubbles&amp;rdquo; than usual.</description></item><item><title>Santo do Monte</title><link>http://example.org/de/wines/santo-do-monte/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 14:29:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/de/wines/santo-do-monte/</guid><description>This &amp;ldquo;Saint of the Hill'' embodies the freshness that a good Vinho Verde should always aim to transmit: a long summer evening in a citrus orchard. It&amp;rsquo;s prickly, it&amp;rsquo;s fresh and its best served cold, even on ice if you may. This should be your new aperitivo, your new &amp;ldquo;Sekt auf Eis&amp;rdquo;, the wine everyone wants you to bring to their dinner parties, lunches or BBQ.
Link</description></item></channel></rss>